talked about you've got some kind of a
gasket or ceiling this is my this is my
favorite ceiling material I have tried
so many I have tried EPDM I buna nitrile
my favorite ceiling material is is a
Teflon rope it's very similar to the
teflon tape you put on threads to when
you thread something in just like you
use just like I used here to thread this
in place yeah the teflon tape there but
it's but it's actually been been spun
into a long cord and that is one of the
best sealing materials ever it is called
teflon rope it well teflon rope some
places call it teflon gasket material
it's it's somewhat expensive you know I
was both to open this but you said it
was about 20 bucks for that right not
really it's probably closer to 10 yeah
probably between 10 and 12 dollars so
how often are you opening this up if
you're using it for you don't have to
open it up if you're if you're using it
you don't have to open it up I open it
up because I'm in the experimenting
phase I wanted to check and see the the
the plates I wanted to see what was
going on in here but if you do now
community dropping stuff that don't you
need to get in there to access it that's
what this is for this is bottom access
be just the elements collected here I
just don't do that drain them off into a
into a gallon jug and pour another
gallon jug in and start over so I don't
have to I don't have to open this at all
once it's once it's sealed up these
these connections here what's what's
that about oh that's just okay here
here's this is the gas out as gas
accumulates in here gas comes out here
and escapes and this is the water in
this can be hooked up to a reservoir I
just connected it to itself for to
transport okay so this connection is not
the way you want to do it in a completed
unit you do this for the sake of trying
to support yeah for transport usually
this thing connects to
a reservoir it goes from here and here
to a reservoir and then goes out I just
put this together so I can carry it okay
Aaron didn't have something flopping
around ready to transport but this is
but you could do it this way you could
do it this way you could just unscrew
that pour out your elements plug it back
in and pour your water or pour your
water in through here and they would
fill up okay so it's it's very simple
very user-friendly once it's sealed you
don't have to take it apart once it's
sealed it's fine I take it apart because
I'm in the experimental phase I want to
test what it looks like in here it's got
jostled around a little bit I'm going to
build a much stronger unit that is that
is actually epoxy together so here in
the future but maybe you can do to look
like off-the-shelf components here what
what are you okay these are this is CP
BC do not use PVC pipe PVC pipe that
goes up to about a hundred and sixty
degrees Fahrenheit see PVC can go up to
210 220 if you're running that hot
there's something wrong but I'm a huge
fan of safety I've burned things up I've
blown things up on purpose not because I
like explosions but I wanted to see what
this can handle so I nated units like
that well I've been holding them we got
to go and they're fine so that's why I
like this see PVC you can't put enough
hydrogen in here with your stainless
steel plates in order to really damage
it this is an off-the-shelf CPVC lid
there about a hundred bucks I just
happen to have one laying around so you
can do many things you can put two of
these on the ends and bolt them together
you can you could drop this unit down
into a five-gallon bucket
don't really recommend it but you could
drop that down until five gallon bucket
and hook up a hose off of it it doesn't
really matter I'm a huge fan of safety
so I like the indestructible nature of
this do you have the dimensions on these
diameters just for this is so I want to
go
recipe this is an 8-inch nominal C PVC
pipe that means that it's about eight
and a half on the outside and seven and
three quarters or actually just under
eight on the inside and these what's up
saving seven eighths thank you do you
have to worry about the cutting getting
rid of any magnetism or whatever that
might build a static electricity in the
metal plates what you see here are
sheared stainless steel plates and we
don't really even had to deal with
magnetism issues like you would with a
conventional Jo cell if you're doing
convinced concentric stainless steel
tubes you do have to deal with magnetism
issues which is very easy to to just
simply use a torch heat them up and take
out the magnetism but with stainless
steel plates just share them don't stop
laser-cut them you laser-cut them it's a
little more expensive than sharing if
you can find a Shearer and say that's a
good way to go I have lots of stainless
steel plates if people want to buy him
pretty cheap too I have lots of six by
six plates so you just stack them
together and pulled them apart with
spacers and then I've got a clamp piece
of plastic that I have laying around the
shop and just clamped it together so
since this is gonna be cut into several
segments let's go ahead and mention your
domain name coming up I'm chemical
hydrogen calm who can ancient tech calm
and tech is Tek yes ancient tech oh and
the other thing that I used to hold this
on is a is plumbing goop that you can
find from Hart from Home Depot
most of them so you put a weight down
okay and then you form your formula gas
and it's actually round completely round
when you start here and that's very
overlaps right on and you get a good
silhouette over there very good yeah
very good seal usually I'll fold it over
the top
I got moved a little bit and see it's
still sealed anyway so that's why I love
this stuff and then I just use a
stainless steel plate that I clamp down
on top this has some grooves in it to
guide the to guide the Teflon where I
want it to go as you can see the grooves
all in there as well just to just to
seal it up very well well that this is
machined here
yes it's machined out I I cut it
actually it was cut for one of those and
I just said you know what I'll just
throw it on here what kind of material
is this this is a 304 stainless since
this isn't being used as an electrolysis
section are assuming it in the
electrolysis section you can use three
or four versus 316 and it's about a
third the prior two-thirds the price
what's that thing on my plates a 3/16
right yes my plates of 3/16 if you think
what neutral of each cell debilitation
of this cell will go up right color you
came with 16 volts and four minute rolls
to each other I'm experimenting
yeah he's experimenting to find find the
best voltage to drop the sound so if I
put two between neutral swallowing it
will generate more heat with it but
journeys but you've got a lot of because
you're putting a lot of power in there I
don't know we're still in the
experimental phase here okay this this
is this this system people have been
probably transmitting elements more than
they realize but this system I've only
been working with for like four months
so this is so so actually transmitting
elements in seeing and seeing all the
ramifications there's it's wide open
right now so I and I encourage people to
experiment I occurred to people to build
these devices maybe get some maybe get
some gold and platinum from ancient tech
and and seat it and start playing with
it people actually somebody asked me in
the elevator about using seawater and be
like the gentleman did in the experiment
or than
in their work to that they electrolyze
the Great Salt Lake water and they get a
lot of gold out from it in I would be
very careful with that because you're
producing a lot of chlorine gas very
very dangerous stuff you definitely
don't want to be running that into your
into an engine you want to be washing
that out so be very careful using
seawater but spring water or miss water
if anybody's familiar with Norma's
distilled water if you use if you're
going to spike it if you're going to put
some gold in there if it's a platinum
iridium something like that is this
purely scientific in other words
whatever elements are in the water are
going to be multiplied or is there some
intention so that human thought and
intention and you know you can create or
diminish depending on intentionality or
is it completely scientific I haven't
seen intention be involved in this yes
but it's still a fairly young field so
we might see more of that in the future
so intention I would I do a little
prayer meditation each day I do I get up
every morning with the Sun and do work
before the Sun and do some do some
prayer meditation and do some Sun gazing
and I put the intention into the day
that the highest and vessel that is
going to happen highest and best is not
always what we want okay is the best is
what the universe has in store for us
it's the path that God has for us you
know however you want to put it the
highest and best may not be what we want
but it's but it doesn't mean that it
always happens
okay but so I try and hold that
intention all day and I try to it's
difficult to work actually in my shop
with a bad attitude and and such you
know based off of you know our
experience with but you've actually
talked about before with
your thoughts and your emotions and our
big energy devices so maybe as we
experiment more we'll see you know maybe
meditation is the best bit ago I mean
I've seen some amazing things done by
people all praying and meditating in
unison around a bowl of water and
manifesting reality outside of
themselves so really amazing stuff so
maybe we'll see more of that as more
people work on this so it's like it's
like the the microchip manufacturers
they discovered that they discovered the
computer manufacturers discovered that
computers work faster when the person
operating them is in the good mood so
instead of encouraging everybody to be
in good mood they started working on
ways to shield their micro processors
from emotions okay
seems kind of counterproductive to me
because hey what if we all got in a
really really good space and we can
create super computers hey what an
interesting idea so I believe okay we've
talked about materials is there any
reason to explain this on base this is
just a base that I use to hold this up
off of the it could be anything
basically it could be anything basically
as a matter of fact I had originally
envisioned this thing flipped upside
down and I wanted to call it my little
r2 unit yes uh-huh
when you put materials in there yes
what's the maximum amount of increase
that you've seen when you put in like
one part of gold you would see maybe you
mentioned early 15 16 times or how you
think I don't know yet we've seen at
least 13 times multiplication as soon as
we get a we know that the elements are
being multiplied because we've measured
it with certain detection devices we
take it away we still got the same
amount that we started with excuse me
and more are over here and we can we can
detect the the elements that are over
here but we don't know exactly how much
is it can see no we see
these 13 times and I'm trying to put it
into circulation recirculation put it
back in
we know I have not yet we and that's
definitely on the list of things to do
is it conceivable that you could have a
continuous flowing of your substance of
the things that you're making you you
seat it with gold for example and then
you run it in it and you pull it off at
a certain rate and you just keep pulling
it off and it's being created from the
hydrogen oxygen gas and the alchemical
process isn't that an infinite scenario
not a
13-fold well I guess I see what you're
saying
it'll be infinite if you just okay I do
turn this off I do you know the Sun Goes
Down and die and it and it's everything
condenses and I take it apart every once
in a while so I don't know the exact
numbers yet you know as we quantify this
where the where they worried in the
advanced theoretical stage here now we
need to quantify the numbers we need to
start figuring out exactly what's
happening here so we can get ratios of
hydrogen oxygen elements generated so
there's a lot of experimentation to be
done mmm
this is a fairly no this is just four
months four or five months old this
particular deal yeah the teflon tape
there but it's but it's actually been
been spun into a long cord and that is
one of the best sealing materials ever
it is called teflon rope it well teflon
rope some places call it teflon gasket
material it's it's somewhat expensive
you know I was good with both to open
this but but I you said it was about 20
bucks for them right not really it's
probably closer to 10 yeah I guess
probably between 10
$12 so how often are you opening this up
if you're using it for you don't have to
open it up if you're if you're using it
you don't have to open it up I open it
up because I'm in the experimenting
phase I wanted to check and see the the
the plates I wanted to see what was
going on in here but if you do now
community dropping stuff that don't you
need he talked about you've got some
kind of a gasket or see this is my this
is my favorite sealing material I have
tried so many I have tried EPDM I buna
nitrile my favorite sealing material is
is a Teflon rope it's very similar to
the teflon tape you put on threads to
when you thread something in just like
you use just like I used here to thread
this in place get in there to access it
that's what this is for this is bottom
access you just the elements collected
here I just don't do that drain them off
into a into a gallon jug and pour
another gallon jug in and start over
so I don't have to I don't have to open
this at all once it's once it's sealed
up these these connections here what's
what's that about oh that's just okay
here here's this is the gas out as gas
accumulates in here gas comes out here
and escapes and this is the water in
this can be hooked up to a reservoir I
just connected it to itself for to
transport okay so this connection is not
the way you want to do it in a completed
unit you do this for the sake of tryna
support
ya for transport usually this thing
connects to a reservoir it goes from
here and here to